I hate California I want to go to East
Coast I want to go where culture it like
me Morgan I recently Connecticut or New
Hampshire and writers live in the
women's of those schools anyway mom
should just go to City College you know
with your work ethic just go to City
College and then to jail and then back
to City College and then maybe you'd
learn to pull yourself up and not expect
everybody to do everything
Lady Bird is that your given name yeah
why is it in quotes I gave it to myself
it's given to me by me Lady Bird always
says that she lives in the wrong side of
the tracks but I always thought that
that was like a metaphor but there are
actual train tracks what she did was
very baller very introduced she has a
big heart ear mom she's warm but she's
also kind of scary you can't be scary
and warm I think you can your mom is so
you're not interested in any Catholic
colleges no way high schools like Yale
but not Yale because I probably couldn't
get in you definitely couldn't get in
does mom hate me you're tired we can sit
up I'm not tying or dragging your feet
you are so infuriating stop yo I'm not
yelling Oh perfect
love it you both have such strong
personalities
when is a normal time do you have sex
you're having sex just wanted it to be
special
why you're gonna have so much done
special sex in your life we're afraid
that we will never escape our past
whatever we give you it's never enough
it's never enough we're afraid of what
the future will bring we're afraid we
won't be loved we won't be like yeah
well you know your mom totally and we
won't succeed I want you to be the very
best version of yourself that you could
be
[Music]
what if this is the best version
what I'd really like us to be on math
Olympiad but math isn't something you're
very strong in that we know of yet
[Music]